Herbert Halpert collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Herbert Halpert's fieldwork
  - Subseries 8: Photographic materials
    - Photographs from negative sleeves (1/3) (Box-folder 77/14)
      - Mrs. Vesty Bell, near Colliers Mill, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 6 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Newbold Prickett, near Red Lion, Vincentown, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Frelen C. Bozarth, Hainsport, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Charles Tilton; unidentified woman, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified woman and (possibly) her second husband, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 6 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Photographs from negative sleeves (2/3) (Box-folder 77/15)
      - John Youmans, South Tom's River, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Anna Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain (brother and sister), 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Ed Chamberlain, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - L-R: John Youmans, Anna Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Photographs from negative sleeves (3/3) (Box-folder 77/16)
      - Unidentified man, of Whitings (possibly a friend of John Webb), 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 1/4 in. x 4 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Tom Test, Browns Mills, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 7 1/2 in. x 4 3/4 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Anne Pomelier, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified woman, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 1/2 in. x 4 3/4 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 1/2 in. x 4 3/4 in. or smaller
      - Frank Reynolds, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
    - Grant Ivins and Charles Ivins (Box-folder 78/1)
      - Charles H. Grant, at Colliers Mill, near New Egypt, NJ, 1938, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Charles Grant, Ivins Grant (brothers), at Colliers Mill, near New Egypt, NJ, 1938, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Landscapes - New Jersey Pine Barrens (Box-folder 78/2)
      - Pine Road, near Lakehurst, NJ, circa 1938-1939, 3 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Possibly a road, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Small pond or other body of water, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, possibly a woodsman, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man at charcoal pit, near Lakehurst, NJ, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - River, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 3 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Road, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 1/2 in. x 4 3/4 in. or smaller
      - View through the trees, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 1/2 in. x 4 3/4 in. or smaller
      - View looking down a road, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - View of trees and brush, in the Pinelands, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 3/4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
    - Photocopies of selected New Jersey photos, circa early 2000s, About 17 manuscript items (Box-folder 78/3)
      These may include images that were under consideration for a posthumous book about New Jersey folk tales. See afc2004008_halpert-pho_notes-mailEnv-xerx.pdf for further details.
    - Photographs without negatives (Box-folder 78/4)
      - Charles Estel, near Hornerstown, NJ, circa 1938-1939, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 5 in. x 3 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Lydia Gyderson, Mt. Holly, NJ, 1938, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, 4 Mile Circle, New Lisbon, NJ, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - Elvin Sweet, Magnolia, NJ, 1938, 4 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller (Box-folder 78/5)
    - New York photo enlargements (1/2) (Box-folder 78/6)
      - L-R: George Edwards, James Edwards, and Frank Edwards (Frank is James's father; George and Frank are cousins), 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, James Edwards (cousins), 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Mrs. and Mr. Charles Seeley, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Charles Seeley, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 6 1/2 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Charles Seeley, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Charles Seeley, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Mrs. and Mr. Charles Seeley, 2 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Charles Seeley, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - Reuben Edwards (brother to Frank Edwards, cousin to George Edwards), 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 6 in. x 6 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Minnie Ward (cousin to the Edwards family), Pepacton, NY, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 6 in. x 6 in. or smaller
    - New York photo enlargements (2/2) (Box-folder 78/7)
      - Shock Wormuth, Shinhopple, NY, 1946, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Two unidentified women (one younger, one older; possibly daughter and mother), 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified older woman (from the previous photo), 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - Martin Montonyea, Sloatsburg, NY, 3 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man and little girl, 3 photographs: print enlargements, black and white; 8 in. x 10 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Swartwout, James Swartwout (brothers), near East Branch, NY, March 21, 1940, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 5 in. x 7 in.
      - Unidentified older man and a cat, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 4 1/2 in. x 6 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified younger man, possible with a pipe stem in his mouth, 1 photograph: print enlargement, black and white; 7 in. x 5 in. or smaller
    - Contact prints - NJ, NY, and PA (Box-folder 78/8)
      Because the 35 mm contact print strips include frames that alternate between New Jersey and New York these have not been separated by state in this finding aid.
      - Charles Bozarth, Tabernacle, NJ, 3 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson, of Retreat, NJ; photo taken at Mt. Holly, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - John Webb, Whiting, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Vesty Bell, Colliers Mill (or Whitings, NJ), 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Elvin Sweet, Magnolia, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Newbold Prickett, Vincentown, NJ, 4 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Ed Chamberlain, Toms River, NJ, 3 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Annie Chamberlain, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Annie Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain; Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: John Youmans, Annie Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain; Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - John Youmans, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified woman, probably NJ, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man (also in the image as possibly the second husband), 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Charles Grant, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man wearing a cap, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 4 in. x 5 in. or smaller
      - L-R: James Edwards, Frank Edwards (father of James), George Edwards (cousin of Frank); Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards (cousin of Frank), James Edwards, Frank Edwards (father of James); Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Frank Edwards (cousins); Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Charles Seeley, Livingston Manor, NY, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man and car, northern NY [there is a dog in one photo], 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Mrs. and Mr. Charles Seeley; probably Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Two unidentified men, probably northern NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - L-R: Shock Wormuth, unidentified man; Shinhopple, NY, 1946, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/4" or smaller
      - Shock Wormuth, Shinhopple, NY, 1946, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/4" or smaller
      - Landscape, Shinhopple, NY, at the edge of the Catskills, near the PA line, 1946, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/4" or smaller
      - James Conklin, Shinhopple, NY, 1946, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 3 1/2 in. x 2 1/4" or smaller
      - Four unidentified children, northern NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Two unidentified men, northern NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Two unidentified women (one younger, one older), northern NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified older woman, northern NY, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Martin Montonyea, Sloatsburg, NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Older man and little girl, possible surname Harris; possibly in Sloatsburg or elsewhere in southern NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Landscapes, NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Tom Test, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscapes, NJ Pinelands, 3 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Anne Pomelier, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscapes, NJ Pinelands, 6 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified woman, NJ Pinelands, 3 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Frank H. Reynolds, NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Elvin Sweet, NJ Pinelands, 5 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man, northern New York, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man, northern New York, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man with cap, on a porch, northern New York, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified younger man, seemingly lighting a pipe, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 35 mm
        See the image in Box-Folder 78/7.
      - Unidentified man, northern New York, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 35 mm
      - Two unidentified men, possibly NY, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 35 mm
      - L-R: George Swartwout, James Swartwout, East Branch, NY, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscapes in charcoal burning, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man, probably PA near the NY state line, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man and woman, probably PA near the NY state line, 2 photographs: contact prints, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
      - Unidentified man (from preceding two images), probably PA near the NY state line, 1 photograph: contact print, black and white; 2 1/2 in. x 2 1/2 in. or smaller
    - Photographic negatives guide (Box-folder 78/9)
      The negatives referenced in this guide can be found in Box 80.
    - Photographic negatives (Box 80)
      These are negatives for prints in the collection (although some prints do not have source negatives in the collection). Box-Folder 78/9 has the guide to the images.
      - Charles Bozarth, Tabernacle, NJ, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Mrs. Julaney Stevenson, of Retreat, NJ; photo taken at Mt. Holly, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - John Webb, Whiting, NJ, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Elvin Sweet, Magnolia, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Vesty Bell, Colliers Mill (or Whitings, NJ), 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Newbold Prickett, Vincentown, NJ, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Ed Chamberlain, Toms River, NJ, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Annie Chamberlain, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Annie Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain; Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - L-R: John Youmans, Annie Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain; Toms River, NJ, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Annie Chamberlain, Ed Chamberlain; Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - John Youmans, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Ed Chamberlain, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified woman, Toms River, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Freeland [Frelen] C. Bozarth, Hainesport, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Charles Tilton, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Stacy Bozarth, NJ, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified man in bib overalls, probably NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified man, probably NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
        A note on the related print says "second husband?"
      - Unidentified man and woman, probably NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified woman, with the "second husband" in the photo, probably NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Charles Grant, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified man, woman, and two little boys, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Unidentified man (without the woman and two little boys), 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm
      - Charles Grant, 1 photograph: film copy negative, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - Samuel Giberson, 1 photograph: film copy negative, black and white; 5 cm x 7 cm
      - Charles H. Grant, at Colliers Mill, near New Egypt, NJ, 1 photograph: film copy negative, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - Landscapes, 2 photographs: film copy negatives, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - Unidentified woman, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: film copy negative, black and white; 3 1/4 cm x 4 1/4 cm
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film copy negatives, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - Unidentified woman, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 1 photograph: film copy negative, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
        Double image, with a close-up of a woman and a three-quarter portrait of the same woman.
      - Unidentified man wearing a cap, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film copy negatives, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - Unidentified man, probably from the NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film copy negatives, black and white; 4 cm x 5 cm
      - L-R: James Edwards, Frank Edwards (father of James), George Edwards (cousin of Frank); Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards (cousin of Frank), James Edwards, Frank Edwards (father of James); Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Frank Edwards (cousins); Livingston Manor, NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Charles Seeley, Livingston Manor, NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - L-R: George Edwards, Mrs. and Mr. Charles Seeley; probably Livingston Manor, NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Reuben Edwards (brother to Frank Edwards, cousin to George Edwards), 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Mrs. Minnie Ward (cousin to the Edwards family), Pepacton, NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - L-R: Shock Wormuth, unidentified man; Shinhopple, NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Shock Wormuth, Shinhopple, NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Landscape, Shinhopple, NY, at the edge of the Catskills, near the PA line, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - James Conklin, Shinhopple, NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Four unidentified children, northern NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Four unidentified children, plus an unidentified man and woman, northern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Unidentified man and woman, with one of the unidetified children, northern NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - Unidentified man, with one of the unidentified children, northern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - An unidentified younger man and woman, and an older man and woman; the older woman is holding an infant, northern NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - The unidentified older woman, by herself, northern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - The unidentified older man and younger man, northern NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - An unidentified younger woman and older woman, northern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - An unidentified older woman, northern NY, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 6 cm x 7 cm or smaller
      - An unidentified man, southern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm or smaller
      - An unidentified man and a little girl, southern NY, 1 photograph: film negative, black and white; 6 cm x 6 cm or smaller
      - Stacy Bozarth, NJ, 6 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscape, NJ Pinelands, 11 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified man, NJ, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Charles Bozarth, NJ, 6 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Herbert Halpert, NJ, 5 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscape, NJ Pinelands, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Anne Pomelier, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Landscape, NJ Pinelands, 8 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Tom Test, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Unidentified woman, NJ Pinelands, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Frank H. Reynolds, NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Mrs. Charles Parker, NJ Pinelands, 2 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Elvin Sweet, NJ Pinelands, 8 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Stacy Bozarth, NJ Pinelands, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Herbert Halpert's cat, NJ, 4 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Santa Claus figure in front of an unidentified courthouse, NJ, 3 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm
      - Inside Herbert Halpert's home, probably NY, 19 photographs: film negatives, black and white; 35 mm